productdesignforums.com 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy - Product Design Forums

**By accessing ProductDesignForums.com you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions of use**

The terms and conditions of use may be changed at any time by ProductDesignForums.com online, and your continued access to the website means that you agree to be bound by the most current version of the terms and conditions of use. 

ProductDesignForums.com and all content of ProductDesignForums.com is protected by copyright and other intellectual property rights. 

All information and materials appearing on ProductDesignForums.com are protected by copyright and are the property of ProductDesignForums.com or the party credited as the poster of the information. 

You may not copy, reproduce, distribute, publish, create derivative works, store electronically, transmit or in any way exploit for commercial gains or otherwise, any content or posted information on ProductDesignForums.com 

If you make postings to ProductDesignForums providing false contact details or impersonating another party we reserve the right to pass your details and IP address on to the aggrieved third party, their agents or any law enforcement agency. 

**Disclaimer**

The information contained on this community website is for information purposes. Whilst every care has been taken in its preparation, ProductDesignForums.com does not make any warranties nor representations as to its accuracy or reliability. We neither accept nor assume any reliability in relation to the contents of these pages which should not be relied upon as accurate. 

In no event do we accept liability of any description for the posting of any unlawful, threatening, abusive, defamatory, obscene or indecent information, or material of any kind which violates or infringes upon the rights of any other person, including without limitation any transmissions constituting or encouraging conduct that would constitute a criminal offence, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any applicable law. 

In no event do we accept liability of any description including liability for negligence for any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use, data or profits arising out of or in connection with the viewing, use or performance of this website or its contents. 

The pages contained in this website may contain technical inaccuracies and typographical errors. The information in these pages may be updated from time to time and may at times be out of date. We accept neither responsibility for keeping the information in these pages up to date nor liability for any failure to do so. 

ProductDesignForums.com has provided links and pointers to Internet sites maintained by third parties. Such linked sites are not under our control and we are not responsible for the contents (including the accuracy, legality or decency) of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. We provide these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by ProductDesignForums.com of the linked site. We are not responsible for the copyright compliance of any linked site. 

ProductDesignForums.com does not warrant that the service will be uninterrupted or error-free or that defects in the service will be corrected. You also understand that we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant that files available for downloading through the Site or delivered via electronic mail through the Site will be free of infection or viruses, worms, Trojan horses or other code that manifest contaminating or destructive properties. You are responsible for implementing sufficient procedures and checkpoints to satisfy your particular requirements for accuracy of data input and output, and for maintaining a means external to the Site for the reconstruction of any lost data. 

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy of our visitors to ProductDesignForums.com is important to us. 

At ProductDesignForums.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit ProductDesignHub.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on ProductDesignForums.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers. 

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**Cookies**

This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties. 

### Third Parties

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

**Spam Defense**

The IPS Spam Defense Service passes the email address and IP address of the registering member to the service to determine the likelihood a registering account is a spam source.

**Invisible reCAPTCHA**

This site uses a CAPTCHA to ensure humans are performing certain actions. The CAPTCHA provider may set a session cookie and get information about your internet browser and device accessing this website.
